Roberto Andrés Alvarado Moreira

Motivated student and programmer dedicated to the study of mathematics and its applications within computer science and web development, also passionate about the new technologies, artificial intelligence, optimization methods and numerical analysis. Searching opportunities to learn and delve deeper into the world of new technological research

robdres123@gmail.com

(+593)988718378

https://github.com/Robdres

Ouito, Ecuador

Tools

Languages 🏶

Programming Languages

Python
MySQL
JavaScript
Java
Latex
Matlab
Rust

Developer Tools

Vim
Git
Figma
VSCode

Platforms

Linux Oocker Ookons

Frameworks y Libraries

Angular
TensorFlow
NodeJs

Skills

Leadership
Critical Thinking
Teamwork
Communication

Professional Experience

Junior Programmer

January,2022-Present

Tecsicom

Quito, Ecuador

With a small group of programmers we were able to create a complete Angular based website for the daily operations of one of the biggest marketing companies in Ecuador

Researcher

June, 2021-Present

Universidad San Francisco de Quito

Quito, Ecuador

Along with all my teammates in the artificial intelligence laboratory in the university, we have used neural networks to learn and create new applications for Al in our environment

Teaching Assistant

June,2022-Present

Universidad San Francisco de Quito

Quito, Ecuador

Loja, Ecuador

I have helped and collaborated with David Hervas, Math PhD, with academic activities

Substitute Teacher

August,2019-June,2020

Colegio de Bachillerato Internacional Antonio Peña Celi

I was able to take part rapidly with high-school activities in order to still

have a great experience in math and physics class

Education

Math mayor

January,2018-Present

Universidad San Francisco de Quito

Quito, Ecuador

Courses: Numerical Analysis, Neural Networks, Differential Geometry, Real Analysis, Stochastic Processes

Computer Science Mayor

January,2020-Present

Universidad San Francisco de Quito

Quito, Ecuador

Courses: Artificial Intelligence, Databases, Computer Architecture, Java Programming, C++ Programming

Philosophy Minor

January,2018-Present

Universidad San Francisco de Quito

Quito, Ecuador

Courses: Philosophy of Religion, History of philosophy, Process Philosophy, Platonic Dialogues

Projects

Neural Networks

June,2022-Present

Universidad San Francisco de Quito

Quito, Ecuador

Inside the AI Lab, I am able to be a part of many computer vision projects, many of them them guided by me. I am able to learn and continue working on actual applications of AI inside our world

Testors

August,2021-Present

Universidad San Francisco de Quito

Quito, Ecuador

I am able to learn and participate in many projects that involve the use of testors, also known as rough sets, in order to reach better processing times